[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What is 15 - 7?",
        "answers": [
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9
        ],
        "correct_answer": 8
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What is 20 - 4?",
        "answers": [
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18
        ],
        "correct_answer": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What is 12 - 5?",
        "answers": [
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9
        ],
        "correct_answer": 7
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What is 25 - 10?",
        "answers": [
            13,
            14,
            15,
            16
        ],
        "correct_answer": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What is 18 - 9?",
        "answers": [
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10
        ],
        "correct_answer": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "What is 30 - 14?",
        "answers": [
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18
        ],
        "correct_answer": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What is 50 - 25?",
        "answers": [
            22,
            23,
            24,
            25
        ],
        "correct_answer": 25
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "What is 27 - 11?",
        "answers": [
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18
        ],
        "correct_answer": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "What is 40 - 20?",
        "answers": [
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21
        ],
        "correct_answer": 20
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "What is 33 - 13?",
        "answers": [
            19,
            20,
            21,
            22
        ],
        "correct_answer": 20
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "What is 14 - 6?",
        "answers": [
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9
        ],
        "correct_answer": 8
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "What is 18 - 9?",
        "answers": [
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11
        ],
        "correct_answer": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "What is 20 - 12?",
        "answers": [
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9
        ],
        "correct_answer": 8
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "What is 22 - 11?",
        "answers": [
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12
        ],
        "correct_answer": 11
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "What is 17 - 8?",
        "answers": [
            7,
            8,
            9,
            10
        ],
        "correct_answer": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "What is 14 - 5?",
        "answers": [
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11
        ],
        "correct_answer": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "What is 10 - 4?",
        "answers": [
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7
        ],
        "correct_answer": 6
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "What is 19 - 7?",
        "answers": [
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13
        ],
        "correct_answer": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "What is 30 - 15?",
        "answers": [
            14,
            15,
            16,
            17
        ],
        "correct_answer": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "What is 29 - 10?",
        "answers": [
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21
        ],
        "correct_answer": 19
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "What is 16 - 6?",
        "answers": [
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11
        ],
        "correct_answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "What is 25 - 8?",
        "answers": [
            15,
            16,
            17,
            18
        ],
        "correct_answer": 17
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "What is 23 - 10?",
        "answers": [
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15
        ],
        "correct_answer": 13
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "What is 50 - 20?",
        "answers": [
            28,
            29,
            30,
            31
        ],
        "correct_answer": 30
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "What is 19 - 9?",
        "answers": [
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11
        ],
        "correct_answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "What is 13 - 5?",
        "answers": [
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9
        ],
        "correct_answer": 8
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "What is 24 - 11?",
        "answers": [
            10,
            11,
            12,
            13
        ],
        "correct_answer": 13
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "What is 17 - 7?",
        "answers": [
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11
        ],
        "correct_answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "What is 20 - 13?",
        "answers": [
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9
        ],
        "correct_answer": 7
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "What is 15 - 4?",
        "answers": [
            9,
            10,
            11,
            12
        ],
        "correct_answer": 11
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "What is 28 - 14?",
        "answers": [
            12,
            13,
            14,
            15
        ],
        "correct_answer": 14
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "What is 11 - 6?",
        "answers": [
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7
        ],
        "correct_answer": 5
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "What is 9 - 2?",
        "answers": [
            6,
            7,
            8,
            9
        ],
        "correct_answer": 7
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "What is 35 - 15?",
        "answers": [
            18,
            19,
            20,
            21
        ],
        "correct_answer": 20
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "What is 14 - 4?",
        "answers": [
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11
        ],
        "correct_answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "What is 21 - 11?",
        "answers": [
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11
        ],
        "correct_answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "What is 30 - 20?",
        "answers": [
            8,
            9,
            10,
            11
        ],
        "correct_answer": 10
    }
]